Tunde J Folorunsho | Software Developer (IT)

 $\ensuremath{\mathfrak{O}}$ London or West midland etc , manchester , willing to relocate

307471013345 / 07424214340

Poltunde@gmail.com

Professional Profile

I am a hardworking, reliable person with good time keeping skills and a good punctuality record. I enjoy learning and have the willingness to learn and acquire new skills. I ampolite, friendly, easy going and a good team player with a great ability to adapt to new or changing environments. couple with leadership experience has a branch managerunder a digital company, ability to adapt to a new technology.

Core Skills

- Business support
- Communications
- Customer service
- Programming
- Campaign management

- Presentation
- Graphic design
- Data protection
- IT support
- Risk management

Career Summary

Oct 2023- Present Tunde Digital World

May 2023 - Aug 2023 Netcom Training, Second line Engineer

April 2022 - Nov 2022 DHL Pepsico - Coventry, (IT)

Oct 2019- March 2022 A.G.G World Limited, Coventry Sales Manager

Feb 2017 - Nov 2021 Skynate Group, Nigeria, Manager

Education

Front-Web Developer. | Bootcamp Edx. | Nov. 2023 - March 2024 | JavaScript, Django, Python, Bootstrap, jQuery, API, React. Node.js etc.

Software Developer. | Code Institute. Dublin | Feb 2022 - Dec 2022 | HTML, CSS, Python, Django, Bootstrap, API, JavaScript etc.

Netcom certificate / Cisco Network certificate | Netcom Training Ltd. Birmingham | Mar 2022 - Aug 2022 | Clouding, Networking, IP Address, Network Maintenance etc.

Degree | Coventry University, | Sep 2019 - Apr 2022 | *Software user: Autocad, Lumion, SketchUp, 3D max, Revit, Project managements * Risk Assessment etc

HND | Federal Polytechnic Bida, Niger State, Nigeria | Jan 2016 - Aug 2019 | Contractor. Site Engineer, Laboratory Test, Structure Calculation.

Diploma | Kogi State Polytechnic, Lokoja, Nigeria. | Aug 2013 - Sep 2015 | Fundamental of Structural and Highway, Laboratory Test.

GCSE | Harmony Secondary School | May 2006 - Mar 2012

Additional

Hobbies & Interests

Volunteering, Sketching, Running, Cooking, Travel, Photography, Fitness, Football, Public speaking

Software

Microsoft office, Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Google Mail, Microsoft Windows, Adobe Photoshop

Hardware

Networking, Printers, CPU, Routers, Servers, RAM, Mobile

Programming Languages

HTML, CSS, Java, Python, C++, C, C#

Languages

English, Yoruba